mp3ify.com 2018-03-14

# mp3ify.com Search Results Page - Online Video Mp3 Converter!

MP3ify Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit MP3ify.com, and how we safeguard your information.

Collection of Information

We do NOT collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc. You may be asked to submit certain information such as your email address to one or more third party entities such as advertisers, a tell-a-friend administrator, and/or a mailing list administrator. Any such submission by you is voluntary, at your own discretion, and is a voluntary submission by you to that third party entity. It is not ever collected by mp3ify.com nor stored by us.

Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

Log Files

As with most other websites, we may collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookie/Tracking Technology and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use mp3ify.com . Cookies can also help customize this site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

We also use third party advertisements on mp3ify.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy please click on the Contact button on the main page.
